oh dear look how many people are on that
can only mean one thing
hello everyone welcome back to hermit
craft the day has come where the flag is
coming down and it's very scary there's
a lot of people on now the vault is a
fit and officially finished I just
wanted to quickly show you and is that
people in the base was impulse it the
seat in what is just vanished the
ceasefire flag is still up they can't be
in the base what's going on I've gotten
rid of all of my useful stuff I don't
want to lose I don't wanna lose all my
tools okay
panic over right so this is the vault
let's go let's go and get prepared ASAP
quickly we need to go to the armory
before we meet everyone at the flag if I
go in here it should dispense everything
that I need
absolutely brilliant so it's impulse
here or not what ok well I'll take the
TNT someone has put some invisible armor
stands to trick us there's actually no
way out of here so I'm going to put that
deity back anyway no time to dilly-dally
and we need to get ourselves together
and meter the flag I think I'm actually
late oh boy here we go I hope you're
ready base because this is gonna be very
explosive I hope everyone's ready look
at look at your uniforms oh my goodness
a scout someone didn't get the memo the
more important question is what are you
guys wearing power ranger at first so
guys I'm I'm having second thoughts
about this you know because I don't know
about you but we've spent a lot of time
building up this base this is like a
whole season's worth of work put in pin
here so you know is it worth it you know
I don't know if I want to do this
[Music]
be quiet be quiet
what is that are you chicken chicken no
no no it could be a chicken
why don't you put your action where your
words are and take down the flag yeah
you take it down I like wood but I don't
even have an axe on me you take down the
flag I don't want to be culpable for
this guys guys guys back to the base
I'll get your stuff G team okay it's
it's happened I
I will admit I didn't really want to
fight them but it's happening cub
clearly wants a fight you know to go
down so some well-heeled EC's gonna be
making some money okay so there's a
relative peace going on at the moment
when the flag came down we've retreated
to our base and we need to actually plan
some stuff out oh I just oh I spoke too
soon
okay okay okay forget that tango tango s
Kel you're on go go to the control room
do the thing do the thing stress you're
with me on the battlefield Kevin and
clear your own defensive duties okay go
go go go go go okay okay okay okay I
can't even see out there why why can't I
see outside my own window stress stress
stress stress on the horses on the
horses if you got the stuff you need
I need shoes okay I mean here's some
potions for us and we got it we got a go
go go go go go go
are you ready yeah okay okay okay come
over here come over here we need to
leave we need to leave via our secret
entrance exit rather okay quick quick go
pick this no stress I cannot stress
enough that there's no time well what
are you doing
stress we meet horses this look like
okay right come chill chill stress right
here come on this is the way we've got
to get out there's nothing I could do
for you now okay get a horse get a horse
and let's get out of here all right I'm
taking this horse let's go we're off I'm
gay we're going straight up Oh Oh the
[\h__\h] the horse is on fire up here splash
no all right okay you ready flying
horses here we go
but no it definitely didn't look well
there goes that plan all right let's go
go go go go go go don't he took like two
hours oh my goodness oh there's so much
going on here
we're not gonna we're not gonna get in
here there's too much fire oh my
goodness I'm just target practice do you
see him oh I'm on fire I don't even know
that what do we do stress this is the
worst attack ever I'm gonna try and I'm
gonna try and take care of I'm gonna try
and take care of impulse oh I've got an
idea
oh this slow falling is the worst I did
I didn't bring milk we've just made this
so much worse for ourselves they have
actually done that much damage to our
base at all right I'm thinking we need
to create a barrier between us and then
here take some TNT we're gonna we're
gonna lay a line okay
and we're gonna blow we're gonna make
our own trench so they can't get past us
so easily if any of them come near we
set it off therefore we should talk
impulse I live I live to tell another
tale oh my goodness what a mess well we
got our wish of a trench
they've got a gas they've got unlimited
oh yeah I'm not sure either of us can
actually get to the other guys machine
go Oh
oh my goodness tango looks so majestic
up there he's like oh hold on I see I'm
I see our man on the inside I'm gonna
I'm gonna I'm gonna have to go off to
the side for a second stress okay I see
our man on the inside I've just messaged
him saying over here Mambo
the sneakiest over here over here over
here over here absolute chaos dude you
didn't tell me that it was gonna be this
crazy I'm trying my best to not kill the
other team no that's fine that's fine I
totally understand wasn't quite
expecting apocalypse being honest yep
so what info can you can you give what's
going on okay we have TMT cannons in the
moat yeah we've got the glass cannon
you've experienced that not as powerful
as we thought so we kind of let down by
that they're like intercom and
intercontinental creepers coming into
your base though in maybe a minute and a
half yeah see see she dog didn't tell us
so he launched them he was like we're in
a time of need we need some lunch
creeper so he launched them and then I
was waiting for something dramatic to
happen but they take three minutes than
that and how did our zombies go did they
do anything they actually they gave us
definitely a bit of a fright but yeah I
mean you know there was four of us down
there it was it went well and it was
very impressive it was very strange
killing zombies with my own head okay so
the quick war is out of the window we're
gonna need this is gonna last a bit
longer than I thought
we're gonna need you to fulfill your
order so what we need to do now is like
organize a little place where we're
gonna exchange information yeah so
where's a good where's a good place for
us to exchange books from this point
forward maybe we could continue using
the shopping district because then you
can go in go into a shop as usual on the
cache on the cache and then every time
we change a note we tell each other
where the next meeting place will be on
the next exchange point is the first
one's gonna be in falses fish shop okay
right okay yeah but we should look like
we're fighting right make sure that make
sure they're watching let's go let's go
and like get in front of people like
maybe I'll let you run I'll chase you
I'll chase you
okay gonna give my bag and I gotta get
you a little bow it looks like looks
like the Fighting's oh I thought the
fighting was over
it's definitely over oh my goodness at
the sound of the tone time is mortal
peril and truer words have never been
written on a sign I think we're gonna
call it I think we've got a retreat
retreat retreat X is hit get him out I'm
getting hit by my own fireballs if they
tried to ease the doorbell I'm back I'm
back I'm back I'm back I know I can see
that they killed Gertrude the witch the
door lady oh my goodness oh no falsies
wearing clears head she's a much better
shot than me yes I'm calling it we got a
retreat retreat
we lost we lost our mat on the ground
retreat retreat we need to go and join
we need to get the high ground retreat
they're retreating as well it's too much
there's too much oh yeah you run we need
to regroup I think and work out our next
point of attack like we neither ever
succeeded minimal damage absolutely
everywhere
minimal damage everybody regroup regroup
at the meeting room shall we looks like
we're safe for now yeah yeah it looks
like we go away with minimal damage
everyone absolute chaos a bit stuffy in
here anyway okay looks like looks like
there was a lot of exchanging of fire
but not actually that much damage
so it looks like this isn't gonna be a
very quick war in the end we're gonna
have to play the long game and we're
gonna have to infiltrate and I think
that's our next bits I don't actually I
couldn't get close the moat was annoying
there was no clear entrance we're gonna
have to find out the weak points we're
gonna have to do some recon and then
we're gonna have to try and make our way
in that way so we've got a plan
carefully but at the same time we've got
to trap our base because it is so easy
to get in our base not gonna so we've
got to make it hell for them everyone in
agreement okay now remember everyone
this war is not a faction war we're not
out just to destroy their base I could
walk in there with 10 stacks of TNT and
end this thing right now but that's not
how we do on the Hermit crossover we
want to have a fun fight okay let's keep
it clean let's keep it me during the
fighting I actually set up my camera
count to watch what was going on it's
not quite as impressive but it here's a
quick time-lapse of how everything went
down this is the time-lapse and it is
pretty chaotic guess who forgot to press
f1 again me so it was absolute Anarchy
but this is a really good opportunity to
tell every single one of you that we had
a great time no one broke any rules no
one was upset we absolutely loved every
second of it and afterwards we all got
in a call and we absolutely giggled and
laughed about how fun it was so please
please please
no negative comments on anyone I want
you to support absolutely everybody's
videos if you can thank you very much
guys also I did actually mention but
we've got some military uniforms which
is really cool this is like my super
British one and everyone has one from
where they're from which is why this cow
was in a weird blue uniform because the
Swedes have got us a strange one that
fight was super interesting at chaotic
and a lot of fun it was pretty much
everything I hoped it would be there was
a couple of hiccups but everything went
pretty well in the end the only thing
that I want to bring up is that Cub
definitely I need to fix this
there's no bucket of water in here the
only thing that I want to bring up is
that Cub definitely did not mean to kill
anyone he told us afterwards he was just
intending to bring the flag down and he
set up a bunch of TNT beforehand so that
he could bring the flag down and I don't
think he meant for anyone to get hurt so
just to clarify that he's not getting
involved in the war at this stage
he's just profiteering from his shop oh
my sweet dog oh who do these belong to
this is straight-up army of them oh my
goodness well we're not fighting with
redstone we're fighting with animals so
now that the war has officially started
we really need to get our act together
we still don't have a lot of the
logistics of our base I think maybe we
should repair some of the damage but in
all honesty there wasn't actually too
much damage done there was a I don't
know how all of these have turned to
stone
I honestly don't know how these turned
to stone this is super weird maybe some
Pistons messed up and we've also
replaced Gertrude she's back thank you
for it free potions Thank You g-force we
probably wants to extinguish some of
this because the entire battlefield is
now on fire it's actually a couple of
days later now so the fighting happened
a while ago but the the world is still
on fire either way
we need to figure out a way to get in
and we need a way to prevent them from
gaining easy access into our base I've
got to admit these signs really didn't
do very well and oh boy I think it might
be cool if we turned this into an actual
light trench at some point I think what
we need to do is get into spy mode and
try and figure out a way to get in to
their base the way that they get in it
would be so easy for us to just charge
him with a bunch of TNT we need to use
their front door and we're not gonna
figure that out without a bit of
espionage so I had that little meeting
with mumbo over there cheering the fight
of all things and we agreed that we're
going to exchange mole reports in the
shopping district and try this is not
good here so while we're both being an
espionage stage I think an idea would be
to make it seem like we've got a secret
entrance like maybe here this would work
quite well so what we do is we we
basically wait until we know that
someone on the Star team or team star is
watching us and then we pretend like we
can't see them and then we've run inside
here and then we hide and then they will
try and follow us in and then set off a
trap that's that's the plan whether it
actually works out that way I'm not
entirely sure
well maybe even could be an actual way
into the base now why is there a sea
lantern right here so what kind of trap
could we put in here well I guess we can
discuss what kind of traps gonna be in
here in the comments however in the next
couple of days I'm going to be uploading
a video with a bunch of trap ideas in it
and maybe we can take a bit of
inspiration from them because I
basically made that video because this
whole thing was going down and I'm
hoping that we can use some of them to
our advantage however because it is
video they will also see them but I'm
hoping that this little false entrance
here could end up being a very cool trap
during the espionage stage of this war
it obviously looks like an entrance or
exit out of the base and that's the
point we really want to lead them in
here we also need to come up with a few
other little traps outside the base so
while we know that they're spying on us
we can trick them into going in and out
of traps like we could even change that
one into a trap we could move the stable
like show them the way in here and then
trap it all so they'll never know which
way to get into our base except there's
a giant hole there hey guys I am I think
I found a floor in our base design I
think the last thing that we need to do
is figure out the place where we're
going to exchange information with mumbo
we need something like a furnace we need
we need a proper a proper thing we need
a chest or something a furnace something
that isn't going to be found again
oh there's a lot of puffer fish for sale
I could definitely use these I might
come back to this shop anyway I have an
idea guys this is how we're going to
communicate I'm gonna take one of these
fish don't worry we're not stealing him
we're just taking him on a little ride
for a second we're going to rename him
hit the button behind the castle times
two and then we're gonna take him back
put him right where he was the chances
of somebody taking this fish while
buying this fish the full Mambo gets his
hands on it is very slim indeed so we'll
put him back in here and then Mambo can
come in here and read this hit the
button behind the castle times two
hopefully he'll City like yes so he'll
look at it and you'll see he'll look at
all these fish because that's why I'm
gonna tell him to do and it'll say hit
the button behind the castle times two
whoa it's stormy up there and then right
under here and then right under here is
where we're going to set up our little
dispenser system so when he hits this
button it should dispense an item so
let's give it a little test there we go
if he dispenses it it will dispense out
his orders now here's the thing I've got
two books and quills here because we're
going to give him two sets of orders
I've just written out both of these so
there's the mole orders now this is very
simple orders create a weapon for Team
star but rigged it to blow up when one
of them uses it and blamed someone on
the G team if they ask okay very very
simple now the second book says the real
orders okay the mole orders are not the
real orders these are you need to game
team stars trusts in order to do that
you need to show them the other book
that you have and let them in on your
secret plan and use it against team G do
whatever it is that they say in regards
to weapons maybe rig it to blow up in
blow up us instead of them or something
the main point is you need to gain their
trust to show that you really are a
double agent and not a triple agent or a
quintuple agent and I forget don't mess
this up mol Mogambo PS good luck from
Jeep so basically what I want him to do
is to go hey hey hey guys hey team star
hey folks hey hey Doc I've just been
given my mole orders here they are and
then they can see yep this looks legit
signed by agreein and everything look
original by Grant and these are the
audience so he can like say like look
guys I've been given this orders maybe
we can use this against them but in
reality he's been told to do that by us
to try and gain their trust hopefully
this works this is like this is awesome
like so he needs to just hit this button
twice one two and out they come easy
peasy lemon
okay there's my little bit of espionage
done we need to get our man on the
inside to do some work for us because at
the moment we know nothing and there's a
lot of info together but we need our man
on the inside to be trustworthy in their
eyes
all right I'm afraid that's all it is
for me this is very exciting everybody I
hope that you've enjoyed it please let
me know all of your thoughts and
feelings down in the comment below and
remember this is all for fun and we're
still all very good friends so no need
to leave any hate and anyone's comments
in fact I want you to support absolutely
everybody including the other team in
their videos thank you very much for
watching everyone and good